Guide to the W. Stebbins Smith Papers 1799, 1840s-1935 MS 575
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Legal Papers (Access Restrictions Apply), 1799, 1840s-1935; 35 Linear feet
  - Unprocessed files, 1860s-1930 (Offsite-box 37)
    Holds, among other documents, the partial contents of various letterboxes, 1904, 1918-19, 1921-22; check stubs, 1860s-70s; Bronx auction catalog, 1899, and other miscellaneous documents to about 1930. Blank forms, especially for Surrogate matters, stationery, and New York Supreme Court print matter. Especially substantive is a circa 1925 study/analysis of the New York City YMCA's program for guidance and placement, and suggestions for those who interview men applying for membership in the Bronx Union YMCA.
  - Unprocessed files, 1850s-1906 (Offsite-box 38)
    Holds typical mix of tri-folded bundles and loose documents on various matters. Checks, 1860s-70s. Pile of insurance policies, 1900s.
  - Unprocessed files, 1850s-1930 (Offsite-box 39)
    Holds typical mix of tri-folded bundles and loose documents on various matters. Bills, 1927. Documents concerning Centenary Methodist Episcopal Church matter, 1880s.
  - Unprocessed files, 1850s-1920s (Offsite-box 40)
  - Unprocessed files, 1860s-1920s (Offsite-box 41)
    Holds typical mix of tri-folded bundles and loose documents on various matters. Checks, 1860s.
  - Unprocessed files, 1850s-1920s (Offsite-box 42)
    Holds typical mix of tri-folded bundles and loose documents on various matters. Many documents relate to compensation claims for the closing of portions of Old West Farms Road between Westchester Avenue and Boston Road, circa 1919-25.
  - Unprocessed files, 1850s-1926 (Offsite-box 43)
    Holds typical mix of tri-folded bundles and loose documents on various matters. Bills, 1926.
  - Unprocessed files, 1880s-1920s (Offsite-box 44)
  - Unprocessed files, 1850-1933 (Offsite-box 45)
    Holds typical mix of tri-folded bundles and loose documents on various matters. Check stubs, 1850s; Bills, 1880, 1930.
  - Unprocessed files, 1870s-1920 (Offsite-box 46)
  - Unprocessed files, 1890s-1900s (Offsite-box 47)
  - Unprocessed files, 1870s-1920s (Offsite-box 48)
    Holds loose documents on various matters. Holds, among other documents: correspondence (partial), 1898; Smith's certificates as notary public for various years to 1921; checkbook, 1870s-90s; print matter; and blank forms.
  - Unprocessed files, 1880s (Offsite-box 49)
  - Oversize documents (flat box), 1875 (Offsite-box 50)
    Holds a volume "Abstract of damage and benefit for the opening of Brook Avenue, from tide water to the Harlem Railroad at 165th Street, New-York" and loose sheets that appear to be copies of the volume.